(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,a,t){},12:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var s=t(0),n=t.n(s),r=t(4),o=t.n(r),l=(t(11),t(1)),i=[{questionText:"How frequently do you eat fried, broiled, or barbequed foods?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Often",ageDelta:4,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Once a day",ageDelta:3,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Few times per week",ageDelta:2,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:1,isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:-2,isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How often do you consume nutritional oils (not fried or heated)? example flax seed oil",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Never",ageDelta:2,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:1,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Once a day",ageDelta:0,isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"2+ times per day",ageDelta:-1,isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How many servings of fruits or vegetables do you consume? (1 serving 2= 1 cup)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:3,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Few servings per week",ageDelta:2,isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"One per day",ageDelta:1,isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"3 per day",ageDelta:-1,isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"5+ per day",ageDelta:-2,isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How often do you consume whole grains and/or natural fiber? (example: whole wheat, pysllium, brown or wild rice)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Few times per week",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Often",ageDelta:-2}]},{questionText:"How many glasses of water do you consume daily? (Water does not include coffee, black tea, soda or alcohol)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Almost None",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"One per day",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"4 per day",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"8 per day",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"10+ per day",ageDelta:-2}]},{questionText:"How many Do you consume sugar, soda, white flour, or other processed foods? (example: canned foods, fast foods, TV dinners, foods with preservatives added) of water do you consume daily? (Water does not include coffee, black tea, soda or alcohol)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"3+ times per week",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Once a day",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Few times per week ",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"How many alcoholic drinks do you consume per week?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"12+ per week",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"8 per week",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"4 per week",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"2 per week",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"How often do you add salt to you food?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"All food",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Daily",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Few times per week",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Once a month",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"Do you take a multi-vitamin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Few times per week",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"Daily",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"Do you take anti-oxidants? (example: grape seed extract, selenium)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Few times per week",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Daily",ageDelta:-2}]},{questionText:"Do you exercise (30 or more minutes of continuous activity)?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Once per week",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"3 times per week",ageDelta:-2},{answerText:"5+ times per week",ageDelta:-3}]},{questionText:'When you exercise, do you do so for more than 2 hours? (If you do not exercise, please put "Almost Never" as your answer)',answerOptions:[{answerText:"Most Times",ageDelta:4},{answerText:"50% of the time",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:0}]},{questionText:"Do you sleep well and awake rested?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Sometimes",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Usually",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"Always",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"How often do you have normal bowel movements?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:4},{answerText:"Every 4 days",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Every second day",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Daily",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"2+ times per day",ageDelta:-2}]},{questionText:"Is there a history of the following conditions in your family? (cancer, diabetes, heart disease, depression, obesity, liver disease, high cholesterol, high blood pressure)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"2 or more",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"One",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"None",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"Have you ever had any of the following conditions? (cancer, diabetes, heart disease, depression, obesity, liver disease, high cholesterol, high blood pressure)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"2 or more",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"One",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"None",ageDelta:-2}]},{questionText:"How frequently do you experience the following conditions? (headache, fever, sore throats, muscle aches (not exercise induced) colds or flu, rash, swelling)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Once a day",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Once a month",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"Almost never",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"Have you ever been exposed to heavy metals or toxic substances? (examples: mechanics, hair dressers, nail technicians, etc..)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Daily",ageDelta:4},{answerText:"Weekly",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Monthly",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:0}]},{questionText:"Have you ever been exposed to heavy metals via dental work or fillings? (example: mercury fillings or other fillings)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"3+ fillings",ageDelta:4},{answerText:"2 fillings",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"1 filling",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"None",ageDelta:0}]},{questionText:"How many full meals do you eat per day? (a snack is not a full meal)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"4+ per day",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"3 per day",ageDelta:0},{answerText:"2 per day",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"One per day",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"None",ageDelta:3}]},{questionText:"At work or at home, how often are you in front of electronic equipment? (example: computers, television, live cameras, electrical wires)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"8+ hours per day",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"6+ hours per day",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Few hours per day",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:0}]},{questionText:"How often are you exposed to cigarette smoke (direct or second hand), or how often do you use a vpae or e-cigarette?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"All day",ageDelta:4},{answerText:"Few times per day",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Few times per week",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"Do you use recreational or street drugs? How often?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"2+ times per day",ageDelta:4},{answerText:"Once a day",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Once a week",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Once a month",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Never",ageDelta:0}]},{questionText:"Do you drive in heavy traffic?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"For a living",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Daily (3+ hours)",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Daily (1-2 hours)",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Almost Never",ageDelta:-1}]},{questionText:"At work and/or home, do you experience stress? How much or how little?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Very High",ageDelta:4},{answerText:"High",ageDelta:3},{answerText:"Moderate",ageDelta:2},{answerText:"Slight",ageDelta:1},{answerText:"Almost none",ageDelta:-2}]}],w=t(2),c=t(5);function u(e){var a=e.setUser,t=e.setShowQuestions,r=Object(s.useState)({}),o=Object(l.a)(r,2),i=o[0],u=o[1],x=function(e){var a=e.target.name,t=e.target.value;u((function(e){return Object(c.a)({},e,Object(w.a)({},a,t))}))};return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"login-box"},n.a.createElement("h1",null,"Get Started"),n.a.createElement("form",{onSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault(),a(i),t(!0)}},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"user-box"},n.a.createElement("input",{type:"text",name:"username",placeholder:"Full Name",value:i.username||"",onChange:x})),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"user-box"},n.a.createElement("input",{type:"number",name:"age",placeholder:"Age",value:i.age||"",onChange:x})),n.a.createElement("input",{value:"Next",type:"submit",className:"submit-button"}))))}function x(){var e=Object(s.useState)(0),a=Object(l.a)(e,2),t=a[0],r=a[1],o=Object(s.useState)(!1),w=Object(l.a)(o,2),c=w[0],x=w[1],g=Object(s.useState)(!1),T=Object(l.a)(g,2),m=T[0],d=T[1],D=Object(s.useState)(0),p=Object(l.a)(D,2),y=p[0],h=p[1],f=Object(s.useState)({}),v=Object(l.a)(f,2),O=v[0],b=v[1];Object(s.useEffect)((function(){console.log(O)}),[O]);return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},m?c?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"Your biological age is ",Number.parseInt(O.age)+y):n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},n.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",t+1,"/",i.length)),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},i[t].questionText)),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},i[t].answerOptions.map((function(e){return n.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return function(e){h(y+e);var a=t+1;a<i.length?r(a):x(!0)}(e.ageDelta)}},e.answerText)})))):n.a.createElement(u,{setUser:b,setShowQuestions:d}))}o.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(x,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},6:function(e,a,t){e.exports=t(12)}},[[6,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.fca29e37.chunk.js.map